A Guide to the Papers of the University Librarian Concerning SOLINET and Library Planning.
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of the University Librarian Concerning SOLINET and Library Planning,
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-12/1/1.051
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
These papers were transferred from the office of the University of Virginia Librarian to the Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library, previous to August 2004 and were accessioned on January 19, 2005.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of the Office administrative files of University Librarian Ray W. Frantz, Jr. (1968-1993) pertaining to SOLINET (Southeastern Library Network, Inc.) and various Library planning and statistical folders, 1963-1991, ca. 3,000 items (7 Hollinger boxes, 3 linear feet).
Arrangement
These papers are arranged alphabetically in two sections, under the headings Library Planning and SOLINET.
Contents List
- Library Planning- Architect, 1973 April- 1975 May (Box-folder 1:1)
- Library Planning- Architectural Advisory Committee, 1976 October (Box-folder 1:2)
- Library Planning- British Columbia, University of Library, 1977 (Box-folder 1:3)
- Library Planning-Cavalier Daily Articles, 1973 December- 1974 December (Box-folder 1:4)
- Library Planning -Clark Hall, 1972 June- 1975 April (Box-folder 1:5)
- Library Planning- Clemons Terrace, 1981 July-1983 June (Box-folder 1:6)
- Library Planning -Collection Development, 1977 November-1981 November (Box-folder 1:7)
- Library Planning -Correspondence with Metcalf, Keyes, 1971 Jul y- 1976 September (Box-folder 1:8)
- Library Planning - Correspondence with Wingate, Henry, 1972 July- 1978 January (Box-folder 1:9)
- Library Planning- Illinois, University of Library, 1973 (Box-folder 1:10)
- Library Planning -Justification for Clemons Library, 1971 October-1981 November (Box-folder 1:11)
- Library Planning- Library Building Committee, 1978 January- 1980 February (Box-folder 2:1)
- Library Planning- Library Building Committee, 1973 June- 1977 December (Box-folder 2:2)
- Library Planning- Library Building Committee -Sprinkler System, 1978 November (Box-folder 2:3)
- Library Planning-Light Wells in Alderman Library, 1963 November-1990 April (Box-folder 2:4)
- Library Planning- Maryland, University of Library, 1973 May-1974 October (Box-folder 2:5)
- Library Planning -Miscellaneous Documents, 1969 October- 1973 January (Box-folder 2:6)
- Library Planning -Non-Print Media Center, 1973 December- 1977 December (Box-folder 2:7)
- Library Planning- Programs, 1973 May-1980 March (Box-folder 2:8)
- Library Planning-Science and Engineering Library, 1984 February-1989 September (Box-folder 2:9)
- Library Planning- Science and Engineering Library, 1964 December-1984 January (Box-folder 3:1)
- Library Planning- Space in Other Libraries, 1985 July (Box-folder 3:2)
- Library Planning -Stanford Library, n.d. (Box-folder 3:3)
- Library Planning- Statistics, CO-2 Forms, 1984 August- 1986 August (Box-folder 3:4)
- Library Planning- Statistics, CO-2 Forms, 1972 August- 1983 October (Box-folder 3:5)
- Library Planning -Washington, University of Library, 1974 April (Box-folder 3:6)
- SOLINET, 1972 March-1987 June (Box-folder 3:7)
- SOLINET- ARL Members, 1980 February-1982 May (Box-folder 3:8)
- SOLINET-Articles of Incorporation, 1973 May-1982 May (Box-folder 3:9)
- SOLINET/ASERL Microfilming Grant, 1989 (Box-folder 3:10)
- SOLINET-Annual Meeting, 1991 April-May (Box-folder 3:11)
- SOLINET-Annual Meeting, 1990 March-May (Box-folder 3:12)
- SOLINET-Annual Meeting, 1989 March-May (Box-folder 4:1)
- SOLINET-Annual Meeting, 1988 February- May (Box-folder 4:2)
- SOLINET-Annual Meeting, 1986 April- May (Box-folder 4:3)
- SOLINET- Annual Meeting, 1985 May (Box-folder 4:4)
- SOLINET-Annual Meeting, 1983 August-1984 May (Box-folder 4:5)
- SOLINET- Annual Meeting, 1983 March-May (Box-folder 4:6)
- SOLINET- Annual Meeting, 1982 April- May (Box-folder 4:7)
- SOLINET- Annual Meeting, 1981 April- July (Box-folder 4:8)
- SOLINET- Annual Meeting, 1979 April-May (Box-folder 4:9)
- SOLINET-Annual Meeting (Box-folder 4:10)
- SOLINET- Annual Meeting, 1976 May (Box-folder 5:1)
- SOLINET-Annual Meeting (Box-folder 5:2)
- SOLINET- Annual Meeting, 1974 March- May (Box-folder 5:3)
- SOLINET-Annual Meeting and Planning Committee, 1987 May-October (Box-folder 5:4)
- SOLINET Board of Directors, 1991 May (Box-folder 5:5)
- SOLINET Board of Directors, 1990 September (Box-folder 5:6)
- SOLINET Board of Directors, 1987 September-October (Box-folder 5:7)
- SOLINET Board of Directors, 1976 October-1979 November, 1982 (Box-folder 5:8)
- SOLINET Board of Directors, 1976 January-September (Box-folder 5:9)
- SOLINET Board of Directors, 1975 January- December (Box-folder 6:1)
- SOLINET Board of Directors, 1974 April-December (Box-folder 6:2)
- SOLINET Board of Directors, 1973 November- 1974 March (Box-folder 6:3)
- SOLINET Board of Directors, 1973 January-October (Box-folder 6:4)
- SOLINET Board of Directors-Conference Call, 1990 June 20 (Box-folder 6:5)
- SOLINET Board of Directors Meeting, 1988 January (Box-folder 6:6)
- SOLINET Board of Directors Meetings, 1977 January- April (Box-folder 7:1)
- SOLINET Board of Directors Meetings, 1976 February- September (Box-folder 7:2)
- SOLINET Board of Directors Meetings, 1975 March- December (Box-folder 7:3)
- SOLINET- Meeting with Ohio College Library Center (OCLC), 1980 November- December (Box-folder 7:4)